Guide to the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace pamphlet and microfilm collection, 1817-1950 MS2110
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Unbound pamphlets, 1817-1950; MS2110 Series 2; 47 Linear feet
  - "United States Trade Promotion Agencies Abroad", 1925 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-31, Author:Foreign Commerce Department
  - "United States Trade Promotion Agencies Abroad", 1935 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-32, Author:Foreign Commerce Department
  - "United States Trade Promotion Agencies Abroad", 1936 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-33, Author:Foreign Commerce Department
  - "Warsaw Rules, 1928", 1929 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-34, Author:Foreign Commerce Department
  - "Wartime National Foreign Trade Week", 1944 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-35, Author:Foreign Commerce Department
  - "Attempts at Freer Trade", 1939 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-36, Author:Grady, Henry F.
  - "International Cartels in the Post War World", 1943 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-37, Author:Hexner, Ervin
  - "The American Businessman and International Arbitration", 1948 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-37, Author:bInternational Chamber of Commerce
  - "Testimony on Cartels", 1940 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-38, Author:Kreps, Theodore J.
  - "Tariffs and Jobs", 1938 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-39, Author:Mullin, Warren D.
  - "The Reparation Dyestuff Situation", 1920 ca. (Box 19, Folder 86)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-40, Author:Patterson, Albert M.
  - "The Foreign Trade of Persia", 1924 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-41, Author:Persia Society, The (typescript)
  - "The Tariff", 1938 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-42, Author:Smith, Dudley
  - "Reparation Payments and Future International Trade", 1925 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-42, Author:bStamp, Josiah C.
  - "America Must Trade Abroad to Preserve Her National Character and Welfare", 1934 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-43, Author:Stimson, Henry L.
  - "Confirmed Irrevocable Letter of Credit Advisable on Shipments to Japan", 1938 (Box 19, Folder 91)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-44, Author:U.S. Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce
  - "Press Release on United States Investments in Foreign Countries", 1940 (Box 19, Folder 92)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-45, Author:U.S. Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce
  - "Foreign Trade Features of the Twenty-Sixth Annual meeting of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States Washington (D.C.) May 2-5 1938" (Box 19, Folder 93)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-46, Author:U.S. Chamber of Commerce
  - "Foreign Trade Problems as Related to Agriculture in the Post War Period", 1946 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-47, Author:U.S. Chamber of Commerce
  - "Commercial Treaties and Trade Agreements", 1923 (Box 19, Folder 95)
    Subject: Foreign Trade; Previous folder number: H-3-48, Author:Whitney, Fred Brown
  - "The Co-operative Movement in the Americas-An International Symposium", 1943 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-1, Author:International Labour Office
  - "Towards Our True Inheritance - The Reconstruction Work of the I.L.O.", 1942 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-2, Author:International Labour Office
  - "The Admission of Germany and Austria to the International Labour Organization", 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-3, Author:International Labour Office
  - "The Eight-Hour Day Act and its Application to Agriculture in Czecho-Slovakia", 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - "Report of Proceedings", 1896 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-4, Author:International Socialist Workers and Trade Union Congress
  - "The International Labor Organization", 1940 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-5, Author:League of Nations Association
  - "About the I.L.O", 1935 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-6, Author:League of Nations Union
  - "World Labor Problems in 1930" (Box 19, Folder 103)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-7, Author:League of Nations Union
  - "World Labour Problems in 1931" (Box 19, Folder 104)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-8, Author:League of Nations Union
  - "World Labour Problems 1934" (Box 19, Folder 105 item 1)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-9, Author:League of Nations Union
  - "Economic Sanctions", 1934 (Box 19, Folder 105 item 2)
  - "World Planning; The I.L.O. and the New Economic Order", 1936 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-10, Author:League of Nations Union
  - "Hours of Work and Employment", 1934 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-11, Author:Macartney, C.A.
  - "World Labour Problems", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-12, Author:Macartney, C.A.
  - "World Labour Problems 1932" (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-13, Author:Macartney, C.A.
  - "World Labour Problems 1933" (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-14, Author:Macartney, C.A.
  - "World Labour Problems 1935" (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-15, Author:Macartney, C.A.
  - "Analysis of British Wartime Reports on Hours of Work as Related to Output and Fatigue", 1917 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-16, Author:National Industrial Conference Board, no. 2
  - "Twenty-Five Years of International Trade Unionism", 1926 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-17, Author:Sassenbach, J.
  - "World Labour Problems", 1937 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-18, Author:Scott, R.F.
  - "World Labour Problems", 1938 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-19, Author:White, J.H.
  - "International Conciliation - The International Labour Organization", 1932 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-4-20, Author:Wilson, Francis G.
  - Committee on Proposed Total Elimination of the Twelve-Hour Day; "Report Presented at the Annual Meeting", 1923 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-1, Author:American Iron and Steel Institute, The
  - "Guaranteed Employment a Wage Plan", 1948 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-2, Author:Berridge, William A.
  - "Mr. Carnegie's Testimony Before United States Commission on Industrial Relations February 5th, 1915" (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-3, Author:Carnegie, Andrew; Reprinted from New York Herald
  - "Men at Work", 1944 ca. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-4, Author:Chamber of Commerce of the U.S.
  - "Resolutions Committee, Chamber of Commerce of the United States: Declarations Adopted by Twenty-third Annual Meeting", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-5, Author:Chamber of Commerce of the U.S.
  - "Proposals of Consideration by An International Conference on Trade and Employment", 1891 ca. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-6, Author:Cond D Liffe, J.B.
  - "The True Solution of the Labor Question", 1886 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-7, Author:Cook, Charles
  - "Your Job in 1940" (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-8, Author:Gannett For President National Committee
  - "Strikes In American Industry in Wartime", 1918 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-9, Author:National Industrial Conference Board
  - "Wartime Employment of Women in the Metal Trades", 1918 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-10, Author:National Industrial Conference Board
  - "Labor Adjustment Machinery", 1946 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-11, Author:Northrup, Herbert R.
  - "Are Labor Conditions a Proper Subject of International Conventions", 1936 ca. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Subject: Labor-International; Previous folder number: H-5-12, Author:Weinfeld, Abraham
  - "The AAA Amendments", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-1
  - "The AAA and Our Form of Government", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-2
  - "Abuses of Power", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-3
  - "Alternatives to the American Form of Government", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-4
  - "The American Bar - The Trustee of American Institutions", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-5
  - "The American Constitution - Whose Heritage?", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-6
  - "The American Form of Government - Let Us Preserve It", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-7
  - "The American Form of Government - The Supreme Court and the New Deal", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-8
  - "American Liberty League", 1934 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-9
  - "American Liberty League Its Platform", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-10
  - "An American Philosophy", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-11
  - "Americanism at the Crossroads", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-12
  - "$4,880,000,000 An Analysis of the Emergency Relief Appropriation Act of 1935 as Approved by the House" (Box 20, Folder 35)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-13
  - "Arousing Class Prejudices", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-14
  - "The Bonus", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-15
  - "Breathing Spells", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-16
  - "The 1937 Budget" An analysis of a Proposed Riot of Extravagance Recommended to the Congress with Misleading Official Interpretations and Representing a Brazen Repudiation of the Economy Pledge in the Democratic Platform of 1932, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-17
  - "The Budget Message", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-18
  - "Budget Prospects", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-19
  - "The Constitution: What it Means to the Man in the Street", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-20
  - "The Constitution and the New Deal", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-21
  - "The Constitution and the Supreme Court", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-22
  - "Constitutional Heresy", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-23
  - "Consumers and the AAA", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-24
  - "Dangerous Experimentation", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-25
  - "Delegation of Legislative Power to the Executive Under the New Deal", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-26
  - "The Dual Form of Government and the New Deal", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-27
  - "The Duty of the Church to the Social Order", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-28
  - "The Duty of the Lawyer in Present Crisis", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-29
  - "The Economic Necessity in the Southern States for a Return to the Constitution", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-30
  - "Economic Planning--Mistake but not New", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-31
  - "Economic Security A Study of Proposed Legislation--Its Dangers, and Its Background", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-32
  - "Entrenched Greed", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-33
  - "Expanding Bureaucracy", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-34
  - "Extension of the NRA", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-35
  - "Fabian Socialism in the New Deal", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-36
  - "Facts About the American Liberty League", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-37
  - "The Facts in the Case", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-38
  - "The Fallacies and Dangers of the Townsend Plan", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-39
  - "The Farmers' Bill", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-40
  - "Federal Bureaucracy in the Fourth Year of the New Deal", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-41
  - "Federal Encroachment Upon the Field of Education in Texas", 1936 ca. (Box 20, Folder 64)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-42
  - "A Federal Union National and State Responsibilities", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-43
  - "Government by Experiment", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-44
  - "The Holding Company Bill", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-45
  - "How Inflation Affects the Average Family", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-46
  - "How to Meet the Issue", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-47
  - "Human rights and the Constitution", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-48
  - "The Imperilment of Democracy", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-49
  - "Inflation is Bad Business", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-50
  - "Inflation and Our Gold Reserve", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-51
  - "Inflation Possibilities involved in Existing and Proposed Legislation", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-52
  - "Is the Constitution for Sale", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-53
  - "It Can Be Done", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-54
  - "The Labor Relations Bill", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-55
  - "Lawmaking by Executive Order", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 78)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-56
  - "A Layman Looks at the Supreme Court", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-57
  - "Legislation-By Coercion or Constitution", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-58
  - "The Legislative Situation", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 81)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-59
  - "The Liberty League-Old Friendships Destroyed", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 82)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-60
  - "The National Labor Relations Act", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 83)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-61
  - "The National Lawyers Committee of the American Liberty League", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 84)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-62
  - "The National Recovery Administration", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 85)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-63
  - "The Need for Constitutional Growth by Construction or Amendment", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 86)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-64
  - "The New AAA", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 87)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-65
  - "New Deal Budget Policies", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 88)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-66
  - "New Deal Laws in Federal Courts", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 89)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-67
  - "The New Deal vs Democracy", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 90)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-68
  - "The New Inquisition", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 91)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-69
  - "New Work-Relief Funds", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 92)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-70
  - "An Open Letter to the President", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 93)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-71
  - "An Open Letter to the President", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 94)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-72
  - "Opinion 148", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 95)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-73
  - "Our Growing National Debt and Inflation", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 96)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-74
  - "Platform of the American Liberty League", 1935 ca. (Box 20, Folder 97)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-75
  - "Political Banking", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 98)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-76
  - "Potato Control", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 99)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-77
  - "The Power of Federal Courts to Declare Acts of Congress Unconstitutional", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 100)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-78
  - "The President has Made the Issue", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 101)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-79
  - "The Presidents 1936 Tax Proposals" (Box 20, Folder 102)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-80
  - "The Presidents Tax Program", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 103)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-81
  - "Price Control: An Analysis of Experimentation Under the NRA, and Recommendations for Future Legislation", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 104)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-82
  - "The Principles of Constitutional Democracy and the New Deal", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 105)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-83
  - "Professors and the New Deal", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 106)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-84
  - "A Program for Congress", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 107)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-85
  - "'Progress' vs 'Change'", 1934 (Box 20, Folder 108)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-86
  - "The Real Significance of the Constitutional Issue", 1935 (Box 20, Folder 109)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-87
  - "Recovery, Relief and the Constitution", 1934 (Box 20, Folder 110)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-88
  - "The Redistribution of Power", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 111)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-89
  - "A Reply to Secretary Wallace's Question Whose Constitution! The Dominant Issue of the Campaign", 1936 (Box 20, Folder 112)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-90
  - "The Return to Democracy", 1935 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-91
  - "The Revised AAA Amendments", 1935 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-92
  - "The Right to Petition", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-93
  - "A Rising or a Setting Sun", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-94
  - "Seventeen Months of the American Liberty League", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-95
  - "Shall We Have Constitutional Liberty or Dictatorship", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-96
  - "Shall We Plow Under the Supreme Court?", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-97
  - "Should We Amend the Constitution to Grant the National Government General Welfare Powers?", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-98
  - "Social and Economic Experiments Under the Guise of Taxation", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-99
  - "Socialization of the Electric Power Industry", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-100
  - "The Spirit of Americanism", 1935 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-101
  - "Statement by National Lawyers Committee of the American Liberty League", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-102
  - "A Statement of its Principles and Purposes", 1935 ca. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Subject: American Liberty League; Previous folder number: I-1-103